https://www.idsuperstore.com/privacy-policy

Best Prices in the Industry
Best Prices in the Industry
Search:
0
Cart
Checkout Now
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Account Login
Forgot password?
Thank you
Your enquiry is on the way. We will get back to you within one working day.
We are commited to protecting your personal information
We take your privacy seriously. This page outlines how we collect, use, share and protect your information.
Information we collect
When you place an order, we collect your:
Full name
Email address
Mailing address
Credit card number with expiry date
Additionally, we monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to streamline the design, layout and features of our site in order to serve you better.
How we use the information we collect
The data we collect allow us to process and fill your orders, as well as update you on the status of your order. We also use your purchase history to personalize your shopping experience by providing product recommendations that might be useful to you.
We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable.
How we protect your information
When you place orders or access your account information online, your transaction is processed using a secure server. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encrypt all the information you input before it is sent to us. This ensures that your information is protected even before we receive it. Furthermore, all of the customer data we recevie are protected against unauthorized access using proven, enterprise-grade industry solutions.
How we share your information
ID Superstore does not and will never sell, trade or rent your personal information to 3rd parties. That is our guarantee.  We may, however, share your information with our partners to perform services on our behalf such as:
Fulfilling orders
Delivering packages
Servicing products
Conducting research and analysis
Providing chat functions
There may be instances where we may be required to share personal information in relation to a regulation, court order, subpoena or government request. We may also share information when we believe it's necessary to comply with the law. We may also share information when we believe disclosure is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of ID Superstore, our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.
We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. You will be notified via e-mail and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership, as well as any options you may have regarding your personal information.
Use of cookies
Cookies are bits of information that are automatically stored on your computer's hard drive to recognize your preferences in order to make shopping easier. ID Superstore uses cookies to help us personalize your shopping experience and keep track of your order as you shop in our online store. Cookies also allow us to recognize you when you return to our site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or any financial information on your computer.
ID Superstore may use reputable third parties to provide services to us, such as to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site, and these third parties may also use cookies on your computer. ID Superstore respects your right to choose whether to be included in the services that these third parties provide. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your internet browser. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser's help section for instructions.
Data retention
We will keep your information in our records for as long as your account is active or as required to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Changes to this policy
From time to time, we may change the terms of our privacy policy to address our customers' changing needs and as required by applicable laws. Please check this page periodically for updates.
Managing your information
At ID Superstore, you have full control of your information. You may choose to:
Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications
Update and correct your personal information
Deactivate your account
To do any of these, please reach out to us using any of the following methods:
Follow the directions in the email that you received from us
Call 1-800-667-1772 with your request and current contact information
Fill out our contact form with your request
Send a letter with your request and current contact information to: ID SuperstoreAttn: Customer Care/Privacy#510 - 250 "H" StreetBlaine, WA, 98230United States
This page was last updated on April 12, 2015.
x
Add to Cart
Retail price:
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price."
As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
You have no obligation to purchase the product once you know the price. You can simply remove the item from your cart.
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price."
As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
You have no obligation to purchase the product once you know the price. You can simply remove the item from your cart.
Need Help? Just Ask! Call 1-800-667-1772
Speak to an ID Expert. Live Chat Now!
Sign up for our Exclusive Deals and Newsletter nowYou'll never miss a deal again
Subscribe
Authorized Partners
Shop with Confidence
Latest from our Learning Center
How Soon Can You Ship My Order?
One of the most common questions we receive from new customers is about order fulfillment.
Here’s
...
Barcode Myths Debunked
Manufacturers and retailers all over the world use barcodes to help them identify their products.
...
What are the differences between NFC tags and QR codes?
Advancements in contactless technology has led businesses to search for the best solution that encou ...
Contact Us
About Us
Copyright © 2015 - 2017 ID Superstore Plastic ID Cards and Card Printer Supplies
